

Phattanothai Pukham



Personal Information

Date of birth 3 may 1993

Nilitary Status Reservist

Current Salary 30000

Date of Availability Immediately

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

Contect

🔲 Tel	0875683762
5 Email	zeref38@gmail.com
Q Address	96 Moo.6 Tambon
	Thanthong, Amphur
	Phan, Chiang Rai
	57250
Github	https://github.com/phattano

https://portfolios.gracia.tech

Skills

Website

30 %		
Coding		
	90 %	
Database		
	80 %	
Server		
	70%	
Research		
	85%	

EDUCATION

2012-2016

Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

WORK EXPERIENCE

GPA 3.21

2021 - Present Freelance Full Stack Developer

10 Nov. 2020 - 2021 Developer at OTEN INNOVAT GROUP CO.,

LTD, Chiang Mai (Remote Work)

1 Jul. 2020 - 8 Nov. 2020 Developer at GWT, Chiang Rai

1 Jul. 2019 - 30 Jun. 2020 Programmer at WORLD GPS TRACKER

LIMITED PARTNERSHIP, Chiang Rai

1 May 2018 – 30 Apr. 2019 Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

E ABILITIES

Coding Python, Nodejs, PHP, SQL, C/C++, C#, Java, Javascript,

Typescript

Flask, Express, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vue.js, React, Nextjs, React Native, Ionic, Jquery

Bootstrap, Material-ui

DevExtreme, Rxjs, Redux, Vuex

One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose

Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Polling, Server Sent Event, Websocket, SocketIO

OpenCv, EmguCV

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g.

sexy, pg, sbobet send sms email, line api

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

Config Replication Master and Slave Server Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Server Ubuntu, Window Server, Nginx , Load Balance, Cluster

Mode, Kubernetes, Docker, Docker Swarm, Kong Api Gateway, Cloudflare, GCP, AWS, Netlify, CircleCI,

Prometheus, Grafana, gRPC, RabbitMQ

General Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana

Researching Microservice, Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, Argo CD,

Jenkins, Apache Kafka, Terraform, Ansible Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase

Robot Framework, Cypress, Figma

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, ASP.Net Core, FastAPI, Rust, Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Truffle, Kotlin, Swift,

Unity, Facebook API, WebRTC